A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.37 (A2012) FA472
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2012.077: Rockefeller Foundation records, grants, 1994-2006; AC_2012_077; 9.58 Cubic Feet 7 standard record storage boxes and 1 letter document box
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - Conference: Social Consequences of Rumor and Legend, 2001-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Social Movements and Contentious Politics in a Democratizing World, 2001-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Conference: Trans/cultural translators: Mediating Race, Indigeneity, Ethnicity in Four Nations, 2002-2003 (Box R3974)
    - Transcultural/translators: Mediating race, Indegeneity, and Ethnicity in Four Nations: Workshop held at the Rockefeller Research Institute, Bellagio, Italy, August 5-12, 2003 - 120 (A2012), 2012:077:006 (Box R3974)
    - BC Team: An American Odyssey, 2002-2003 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Cultural Protection and Sex Equality, 2002-2003 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Developing, Naming and Dissemination of Diagnostic and Prognostic Tests for Learning Disabilities in Palestinian and Israeli Children and Youth, 2002-2004 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: An Electronic Edition of Dante's "Commedia", 2002-2003 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Ethnicity, Trust and Transition in Postcommunist Society, 2002-2004 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Global Dialogues on Intellectual Property: Call of the Earth Dialogue: Organizers, 2003-2004 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Global Dialogues on Intellectual Property: Food Security, Plant Genetic Resources and IP, 2003 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Global Dialogues on Media and Social Change: Media and War in South Asia, 2003 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Global Dialogues on Media and Social Change: Media, Freedom, and Poverty, 2003-2004 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Global Dialogues on Transitional Justice: Repairing the Past - Reparations and Transitions to Democracy, 2003-2004 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Global Dialogues on Transitional Justice: Truth Commission and NGOs: The Essential Relationship, 2003 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: 'Kimihia te mea ngaro' (Seek What is Hidden): Preserving and Distributing Endangered Indigenous Language Print Collections, 2001-2004 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Middle Eastern Islam from Afar: South/Southeast Asian and African Perspectives, 2001-2003 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Museums and Global Public Spheres: Editorial Meeting, 2002-2003 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Potential of Membrane Technology for Sustainable Decentralized Sanitation, 2002-2004 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Reducing Mortality and Improving Quality of Life in Long-term Survivors of Hodgkin's Disease, 2002-2004 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Sine Die: A Multimedia Work, 2002-2003 (Box R3976)
    - BC Team: Women Writing Africa: Eastern Region, 2002-2003 (Box R3976)
- AC.2012.081: Rockefeller Foundation records, grants, 2001-2006; AC_2012_081; 9.58 Cubic Feet 7 standard record storage boxes and 1 letter document box
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), 9.58 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes and 1 letter document box
    - National Alliance of Media Arts Centers - 16th Biennial Conference - 2002 CC 045, 2001-2004 (Box R3977)
    - Pull Focus, Pushing Forward: media arts connecting culture andcommunity. 2002 namac conference - videos and reports - Seattle, Washington. 2002 cc 045, 2012:081:001 (Box R3977)
    - Performance Space 122 - New Theater Project 2002 CC 049, 2002-2004 (Box R3977)
    - Fresh Terrain - Student Documentary 2002 cc 049 (A12), 2012:081:015 (Box R3977)
    - City Limits Community Information Service, Inc. - Arts and Culture and Community Development Project Focused on NYC - 2002 CC 050, 2002-2003 (Box R3977)
    - Theatreworks (Singapore) - "The Continuum Asia Project" - 2002 CC 054, 2001-2005 (Box R3977)
    - Untitled, 2012:081:002 (Box SF1)
    - Visiting Asian Artists Workshops, Feb 03, 2003; 2012:081:003 (Box SF1)
    - Mekong Diaries, Video Works by 13 Youth of Luang Prabang 2002 cc 054 (A12), 2012:081:004 (Box R3977)
    - Mekong Diaries, Video Works by 13 Youth of Luang prabang 2002 cc 054 (A12), 2012:081:005 (Box R3977)
    - Theatreworks (Singapore) - "The Continuum Asia Project" Excavating Cultural memories: The Revival of Phralak Phralam July to November 2003 Report - 2002 CC 054, 2012:081:006 (Box R3977)
    - Theatreworks (Singapore) - "The Continuum Asia Project" Excavating Cultural Memories: The Revival of Phralak Phralam July to November 2003 Report 2002 CC 054, 2012:081:008 (Box R3977)
    - Theatreworks (Singapore) - "The Continuum Asia Project" Excavating Cultural Memories: The Revival of Phralak Phralam July to November 2003 Report - 2002 CC 054, 2012:081:007 (Box R3977)
    - Theatreworks (Singapore) - "The Continuum Asia Project" Excavating cultural memories: The Revival of Phralak Phralam July to November 2003 A documentary by Oak3films - 2002 cc 054, 2012:081:009 (Box R3977)
    - Theatreworks (Singapore) - "The Continuum Asia Project" MeKong Diaries, 2002 CC 054, 2012:081:010 (Box R3977)
    - Theatreworks (Singapore) - "The Continuum Asia project" Mekong Diaries, A documentary by Oak3films 2002 CC 054, 2012:081:011 (Box R3977)
    - Theatreworks (Singapore) - "The Continuum Asia Project" In Collaboration with the Children's Cultural Centre, Luang Probang, Laos - Mekong Diaries: 13 Video documentary shorts by Luang Probang Youth with support from the Rockefeller Foundation 2002 CC 054, 2012:081:012 (Box R3977)
    - Theatreworks (Singapore), Theatreworks (Laos) - (1) Excavating Memories; (2) Mekong Diaries 2002 CC 054, 2012:081:013 (Box R3977)
    - City University of New York - M.A. Program in Latin American, Caribbean and Latino Studies - 2002 CC 056, 2001-2004 (Box R3977)
    - Museum of Spanish Colonial Art - Exhibition, "Conexiones" - 2002 CC 059, 2000-2003 (Box R3977)
    - Untitled, 2012:081:014 (Box SF1)
    - Spanish New Mexico: The Spanish Colonial Arts Society Collection, 2002 cc 059 (A12), 2010:081:020 (Box R3977)
    - Conexiones: Connections in Spanish Colonial Art, 2002 cc 059 (A12), 2012:081:021 (Box R3977)
    - New Museum of Contemporary Art - Publication, "Over Here..." 2002 CC 060, 2001-2004 (Box R3977)
    - Over Here: International Perspectives on Art and Culture, Edited by Gerardo Mosquera and Jean Fisher, 2002 CC 060 (A12), 2012:081:022 (Box R3977)
    - Out There: Marginalization and Contemporary Cultures, Edited by Russell Ferguson, Martha Gever, Trinh T. Minh-ha, and Cornel West 2002 cc 060, 2012:081:023 (Box R3977)
    - San Diego Museum of Art - Exhibition, "Axis Mexico" - 2002 CC 061, 2001-2003 (Box R3977)
    - Untitled, 2012:081:016 (Box SF1)
    - Full Focus: "Axis Mexico" 2002 cc 061 (A12), 2012:081:017 (Box R3977)
    - Axis Mexico "The Lounge" Betti-Sue Hertz, 2002 cc 061 (A12), 2002 October 7; 2012:081:018 (Box R3977)
    - Axis Mexico: Common Objects and Cosmopolitan Actions/Objetos Comunes Y Acciones Cosmopolitas; 2002 cc 061 (A12), 2012:081:019 (Box R3977)
    - Aspen Institute: Needs Assessment Conference, "The Humanities and the New Communications Environment" - 2002 CC 062, 2002-2004 (Box R3977)
    - WBEZ Alliance, Inc. - Second Annual 3rd Coast International Audio Festival - 2002 CC 063, 2002-2003 (Box R3977)
    - 2002 Third Coast International Audio festival Broadcast, [Hour One] 2002 CC 063, 2012:081:024 (Box R3977)
    - 2002 Third Coast International Audio Festival Broadcast, [Hour Two], 2002 CC 063, 2012:081:025 (Box R3977)
    - Location One - Enable Not-for-profits to Create Collaborative Interface for Artistic Works - 2002 CC 066, 2001-2003 (Box R3978)
    - Trans-Local; proudced by Location One; 2002 cc 066 (A12), 2012:081:026 (Box R3978)
    - Rhizome Communications - Ongoing Activities - 2002 CC 067, 2001-2003 (Box R3978)
    - Hip Hop Theatre Junction - Third Annual NYC Festival - 2002 CC 068, 2002-2004 (Box R3978)
    - American Federation of Arts - Exhibition, "The Sensuous and the Sacred" - 2002 CC 069, 2001-2003 (Box R3978)
    - The Sensuous and the Sacred: Chola Bronzes from South India; A Resource for Teachers American Federation of Arts 2002 cc 069, 2012:081:027 (Box R3978)
    - The Sensuous and the Sacred: Chola Bronzes fromSouth India; A Resource for Teachers American Federation of Arts. 2002 cc 069, 2012:081:028 (Box R3978)
    - New York University - Exhibition, "Between Word and Image: Modern Iranian Visual Culture" - 2002 CC 071, 2001-2004 (Box R3978)
    - Untitled - 2002 cc 071 (A12), 2012:081:029 (Box SF1)
    - Picturing Iran: Art, Society and revolution: Edited by Shiva Balaghi and Lynn Gumpert. 2002 cc 071, 2012:081:030 (Box R3978)
    - University of South Florida - Exhibition, "The Field's Edge: Agency, Body and the African Lens" - 2002 CC 072, 2001-2004 (Box R3978)
    - Brooklyn Philmarmonic Symphony Orchestra - Consortium of Brooklyn Cultural Institutions - 2002 CC 076, 2002-2003 (Box R3978)
    - Asian American Arts Alliance - Post 9/11 Assistance to Arts Organizations - 2002 CC 077, 2002-2003 (Box R3978)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts - Arts Leadership Initiative and post 9/11 Capacity Building for African-American Arts Organizations - 2002 CC 079, 2002-2003 (Box R3978)
    - Leonardo - Development of "Arts Lab" - 2002 CC 084, 2001-2005 (Box R3978)
    - International Arts Federation Services Pty (Australia) - Ongoing Activities - 2002 CC 085, 2002-2004 (Box R3978)
    - Lower East Side Tenement Museum - International Coalition of Historic Site Museums of Conscience - 2002 CC 088, 2000-2003 (Box R3979)
    - Brandeis University - Exhibition, "Coexistence: Contemporary Cultural Production in South Africa" - 2002 CC 089, 2001-2003 (Box R3979)
    - Coexistence: Contemporary Cultural production in South Arica 2002 cc 089 (A12), 2012:081:031 (Box R3979)
    - Untitled, 2012:081:032 (Box SF1)
    - Untitled, 2012:081:033 (Box SF1)
    - Calista Elders Council - Yup'ik Voices" Book - 2002 CC 090, 2002-2004 (Box R3979)
    - National Association of Latino Arts and Culture - 2002 Annual Conference, "New Americas: A Transnational Paradigm" - 2002 CC 091, 2002-2004 (Box R3979)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Teacher Education Colaborative - 2002 CC 093, 2001-2005 (Box R3979)
    - Creative Time - Media Exhibition, "Consuming Places" - 2002 CC 096, 2002-2003 (Box R3979)
    - Untitled, 2012:081:034 (Box SF1)
    - Smithsonian Institution - Project, "The Edge of Enchantment" - 2002 CC 097, 2001-2005 (Box R3979)
    - Brown University - Multi-Media Exhibition, "911+1: The Art of War in the Information Age" - 2002 CC 101, 2001-2003 (Box R3979)
    - Brown University - "9+11" 2002 cc 101, 2012:081:035 (Box R3979)
    - Info, Tech, War, Peace: The Information Technology, War and Peace Project, 2002 cc 101 (A12), 2012:081:036 (Box R3979)
    - Info, Tech, War, Peace: After 911, 2002 cc 101, 2012:081:037 (Box R3979)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Race and Technology - 2002 CC 102, 2001-2004 (Box R3979)
    - Young People's Chorus of New York City - Music Education and Choral Performance Programs - 2002 CC 110, 2002-2004 (Box R3979)
    - Transient Glory: The Young People's Chorus of New York: 2002 cc 110 (A12), 2012:081:038 (Box R3979)
    - 33 Fainting Spells - "Our Little Sunbeam" - 2002 CC 112, 2002-2004 (Box R3979)
    - Alley Theatre - "Cantinflas" - 2002 CC 113, 2002-2004 (Box R3979)
    - American Repertory Theater - Music-Theater Work, "Story In Story Out" - 2002 CC 114, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Avaz International Dance Theatre - "Bahram E-Gur" - 2002 CC 116, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Bang on a Can - Commissioning and Production of New Work - 2002 CC 117, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Bang on a Can All Stars performing with Kyaw Kyaw Naing 2002 cc 117, 2012:081:039 (Box R3980)
    - Bang on a Can Meets Kyaw Kyaw Naing, 2002 cc 117, 2012:081:040 (Box R3980)
    - Big Dance Theater - Dance Theater Piece, "Antigone", 2002-2003 (Box R3980)
    - Builders Association - Crossmedia project, "Alladeen" - 2002 CC 119, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Untitled, 2012:081:041 (Box R3980)
    - Chitresh Das Dance Co. - "East as Center" - 2002 CC 120, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Circus Amok - "Homeland Security: The Williamsburg Project" - 2002 CC 121, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Cornerstone Theater Co. "Gay, Lesbian and Transgender People of Faith Project" - 2002 CC 122, 2002-2003 (Box R3980)
    - Dancers' Group - "Onion" - 2002 CC 123, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Dansology - "Mech(A)" - 2002 CC 124, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Earshot Jazz - "Joe Hill" - 2002 CC 125, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Edith Kanak'ole Foundation - Dance Piece, "Hanau Ka Moku: An Island Is Born" - 2002 CC 126, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Everett Dance Theatre - "Home Movies" - 2002 CC 127, 2002-2005 (Box R3980)
    - Ping Chong and Co. - "The Africa Project" - 2002 CC 128, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Fund For Women Artists - "The Rose Project" - 2002 CC 129, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Helena Presents - "Geyser Land" - 2002 CC 130, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Inta - "Offering" - 2002 CC 131, 2002-2005 (Box R3980)
    - International Wow Co. - Original Theater Piece, "Death of Nations" - 2002 CC 132, 2002-2003 (Box R3980)
    - Jose Limon Dance Foundation - New Work - 2002 CC 133, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Jump Start Performance Co. Multi-Media Theater Production "Cameoland" 2002 CC 134, 2002-2003 (Box R3980)
    - Jump Street Company - "Cameoland" 2002 CC 134 (A12), 2012:081:042 (Box R3980)
    - 651 Arts 0 "Black Burlesque (Revisited)" 2002 CC 135, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Black Burlesque (revisited) Acts I and II, 2002 CC 135 (A12), 2012:081:043 (Box R3980)
    - Kronos Quartet - "Sun Rings" 2002 CC 136, 2002-2003 (Box R3980)
    - Mabou Mines - "Cara Lucia" 2002 CC 137, 2002-2003 (Box R3980)
    - Guild Complex - "Sisters in the Smoke" 2002 CC 138, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Mettawee River Theatre Co. - "The Blue Hole Tabernacle Revival" 2002 CC 139, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - Miami-Dade Community College - "The Human tragedy of Genocide, Rwanda and Tomorrow?" 2002 CC 140, 2002-2004 (Box R3980)
    - New York City Players; "Joe" 20002 CC 142, 2002-2003 (Box R3981)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts - "Nomad I: Tea" 2002 CC 143, 2002-2004 (Box R3981)
    - Performing Artservices - "Celestial Excursions" 2002 CC 144, 2000-2004 (Box R3981)
    - Providence Productions International - "Jenkins2" 2002 CC 145, 2002-2004 (Box R3981)
    - Red Wing Performing Group - "The Hiroshima Maidens Project" 2002 CC 146, 2002-2004 (Box R3981)
    - Relache - "Broken" 2002 CC 147, 2002-2004 (Box R3981)
    - The Bell and the Glass, Philadelphia Museum of Art, 2002 CC 147 (A12), 2012:081:044 (Box R3981)
    - Shadowlight Productions - "The Seven Visions of Encarnacion" 2002 CC 149, 2002-2003 (Box R3981)
    - ShadowLight Productions; The 7 Visions of Encarnacion, 2002 November 8; 2012:081:045 (Box R3981)
    - Thin Man Dance - "Teathered to Wind" 2002 CC 150, 2002-2004 (Box R3981)
    - Walker Art Center - Development and Production of "Braff's Neck" 2002 CC 151, 2002-2004 (Box R3981)
    - Banff Centre for Continuing Education (Canada) - Bridges Two Conference 2002 CC 152, 2002-2003 (Box R3981)
    - Bridges: International Consortium on Collaboration in Art and Technology; Bridges II 2002 CC 152 (A2), 2002 October 4-6; 2012:081:046 (Box R3981)
    - Bridges: International Consortium on Collaboration in Art and Technology; Bridges II 2002 CC 152 (A2), 2002 October 4-6; 2012:081:047 (Box R3981)
    - On the Boards - "Listening Post" 2002 CC 153, 2002-2003 (Box R3981)
    - Listening Post: Mark Hansen and Ben Rubin, 2002 CC 153, 2012:081:048 (Box R3981)
    - The Kitchen - Discussion Series, "Digital H@ppy Hours" 2002 CC 154, 2002-2004 (Box R3981)
    - Center for Arts and Culture - Programs re Creative Sector and Cultural Diplomacy 2002 CC 155, 2002-2003 (Box R3981)
    - Art Science Collaborations - ARTSCI2002 Symposium 2002 CC 157, 2002-2003 (Box R3981)
    - Legacy Project - Conference and Exhibition on Aftermath of 9/11 - 2002 CC 158, 2002-2004 (Box R3981)
    - Field Museum of Natural History - International Symposium and Art Exhibit on Hip Hop Culture 2002 CC 159, 2002-2004 (Box R3981)
    - Internews Interactive - Documentary Project, "Vis A Vis: Native Tongues" 2002 CC 160, 2002-2004 (Box R3981)
    - State University of New York - Exhibition of Photography and Video from Cuba (New Paltz) 2002 CC 163, 2002-2003 (Box R3981)
    - Untitled, 2002 CC 103, 2012:081:049 (Box SF1)
    - Homelands Productions - Radio Documentary Series, "Worlds of Difference" 2002 CC 164, 2002-2006 (Box R3981)
    - Worlds of Difference: Cultural Diversity in a Global Age; A Radio Documentary Project of Homelands Production 2002 CC 164 (A12), 2012:081:050 (Box R3981)
    - Worlds of Difference: Cultural Diversity in a Global Age - Pieces Broadcast 2002 CC 164, 2002 October 1 - 2003 September 30; 2012:081:051 (Box R3981)
    - Worlds of Difference Special: Local Culture in a Global Age; A Radio Documentary Project of Homelands Production. 2002 CC 164, 2012:081:052 (Box R3981)
    - New York Digital Salon - 2003 International Symposium 2002 CC 165, 2002-2003 (Box R3981)
    - Social Science Research Council - Conservation of Hemingway Papers 2002 CC 167, 2002-2003 (Box R3981)
    - Council for Aid to Education - Closing Post - Secondary Education Gaps 2002 CC 169, 2002-2004 (Box R3982)
    - Latino Theatre Co. - "Dementia" 2002 CC 173, 2002-2004 (Box R3982)
    - University of Texas - Workshop on Economic Implications of Fair Use (Austin) 2002 CC 174, 2002-2004 (Box R3982)
    - Wilson, Woodrow (National Fellowship) Foundation - Public Scholarship Grants 2002 CC 180, 1999-2004 (Box R3982)
    - UNESCO Institute for Statistics (Canada) - International Symposium on Cultural Statistics 2002 CC 181, 2002-2004 (Box R3982)
    - Actes du Colloque International sur les statistiques culturelles - Proceedings of the International Symposium on Culture Statistics, 2002 CC 181, 2012:081:053 (Box R3982)
    - Apollo Theater Foundation - "Harlem Song" 2002 CC 184, 2002-2003 (Box R3982)
    - Bay Area Video Colalition - Digital Storytelling Project for Youth 2002 CC 196, 2002-2003 (Box R3982)
    - BrainGlow: Ideas and Tools for Digital Storytelling, 2002 CC 196 (A12), 2012:081:054 (Box R3982)
    - Bang on a Can - "2003 E-Festival" 2002 CC 197, 2002-2004 (Box R3982)
    - Stanford University - Research Project, "Modes of Knowledge and Language Ambiguity" 2002 CC 199, 2002-2004 (Box R3982)
    - Chicago Tourism Board - "Advancing Chicago's Civic Agenda Through the Arts" 2002 CC 201, 2002-2004 (Box R3982)
    - Waag Society (Netherlands) - "My First Recession" 2002 CC 202, 2002-2004 (Box R3982)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art - Exhibition,"The American Effect" 2002 CC 205, 2002-2004 (Box R3982)
    - The Amaerican Effect: Global Perspective on the United States, 1990-2003, 2002 CC 205, 2012:081:055 (Box R3982)
    - New York Theatre Workshop - Artists Residency Program at Vassar and Dartmouth 2002 CC 206, 2002-2004 (Box R3982)
- AC.2012.085: Rockefeller Foundation records, grants, 1990-2007; AC_2012_085; 7.89 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes
  - Communication for Social Change (CS), 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - International Center for Tropical Agriculture (Columbia) - Impact of Community Telecenters 2000 CS 007, 2000-2004 (Box R3983)
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - World Music Productions - Preserve, Document and Disseminate Music From Africa and Other Cultures 2002 CC 215, 2002-2004 (Box R3983)
    - Sponge - Digital Networks and Networked Environments 2002 CC 217, 2002-2005 (Box R3983)
    - Joy2Learn Foundation - Internet-based Visual and Performing Arts Education Programs for Schools 2002 CC 219, 2001-2005 (Box R3983)
    - Joy2Learn Foundation Presents Piano Music Featuring Alan Gampel, 2002 cc 219 (A12), 2012:085:002 (Box R3983)
    - George Lucas Foundation - Digital Promise 0 Video, AVI Mega Video 4:13, 2002 cc 219 (A12), 2012:085:003 (Box R3983)
    - Joy2Learn Foundation Presents Theater with Hector Elizondo 2001 cc 224 (A12), 2012:085:006 (Box R3984)
    - Exit Art/The First World - Exhibition, "The L-Factor" 2003 CC 003, 2002-2004 (Box R3983)
    - University of California, Berkeley - Exhibition of Works of Jun Nguyen-Hatsushiba 2003 CC 012, 2002-2004 (Box R3983)
    - Jun Nguyen-Hatsushiva; Memorial Project Nha Trang, Vietnam: Towards the Complex: Courageous, the Curious, and the Cowards (2001) 2003 cc 012 (A12), 2012:085:004 (Box R3983)
  - Food Security (FS), 7.89 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
    - John Innes Centre (England) - Studentships for Cooperative Program on Rice Biotechnology 2000 FS 003, 1999-2004 (Box R3983)
    - Abolade Afolabi, Thesis. 2000 FS 003 (A12), 2013:085:001 (Box R3983)
    - International Center for tropical Agriculture (Columbia) - Molecular Mapping of Genes and Cassava Mosaic Disease 2000 FS 004, 1996-2003 (Box R3983)
    - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (India) - Molecular Genetic Analysis and Drought Tolerance in Cereals 2000 FS 018, 2001-2004 (Box R3983)
    - Zhejiang Agricultural University (China) - Insect Resistance in Transgenic Rice 2000 FS 020, 1997-2004 (Box R3983)
    - Purdue University - Striga Resistance in Sorghum 2000 FS 024, 1999-2004 (Box R3983)
    - University of Agricultural Sciences (India) - Molecular Markers for Drought Tolerance in Rainfed Rice Breeding Program, 2000-2005 (Box R3984)
    - Ndjiondjop Nzenkam, Marie-Noelle - Molecular Markers and Resistance to Rice Yellow Mottle Virus 2000 FS 047, 1998-2004 (Box R3984)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - Integrated Pest Management of Cassava Mosaic Disease in East Africa; Training for African students 2000 FS 053, 2000-2004 (Box R3984)
    - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (Nigeria) - Molecular Mapping and Casssava Mosaic Disease 2000 FS 056, 1995-2003 (Box R3984)
    - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (Nigeria) - Banana Pests Control 2000 FS 066, 1990-2004 (Box R3984)
    - Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology (Kenya) - Field Training; Pigeon Pea Production, 1999-2003 (Box R3984)
    - Youth For Action - Strengthen Farmers' Capacity; Participatory Model for Agricultural Technology in India 2000 FS 081, 2000-2004 (Box R3985)
    - Central Research Institute for Food Crops (Indonesia) - Rice Cultivars Improved with Leaf Blight Resistance, 2000-2006 (Box R3985)
    - University of Zimbabwe - Multicropping for Soil Improvement, 2000-2002 (Box R3985)
    - Moi University (Kenya) - Field Training; Sociology of Agroforestry Adoption 2000 FS 091, 1999-2005 (Box R3985)
    - University of Zimbabwe - Improve Disease Resistance of Cowpea Through Genetic Engineering 2000 FS 094, 2000-2005 (Box R3985)
    - University of Malawi - Striga Management in Maize-Based Production Systems 2000 FS 097, 1993-2004 (Box R3985)
    - Thailand - Agriculture (Dept. of) - Bacterial Blight and Blast Resistance in Rice 2000 FS 105, 2000-2002 (Box R3985)
    - International Center for the Information on Cover Crops (Honduras) - Green Manure Cover Crop Database 2000 FS 125, 2000-2004 (Box R3985)
    - Zimbabwe Institute of Permaculture - Documentation and Expansion of Scope Program 2000 FS 097, 2000-2004 (Box R3985)
    - Kenya Agricultural Research Institute - Banana Improvement Through Biotechnology 2000 FS 135, 2000-2004 (Box R3985)
    - Malawi - Agriculture and Irrigation (Ministry of) - Integrated Soil Fertility Management 2000 FS 139, 2000-2007 (Box R3985)
    - International Center for Maize and Wheat Improvement (Mexico) - Soil Fertility Research Network for Smallholder Maize-Based Cropping Systems in Southern Africa (2 + 1 Supplemental Folder) 2000 FS 140, 1994-2004 (Box R3986)